<resources>
    <string name="app_name">PrivaDroid</string>

    <string name="agree_to_terms">Agree to terms above</string>
    <string name="continue_app_settings_button">Continue</string>
    <string name="terms_title">Terms</string>
    <string name="terms_description">
        PrivaDroid is a community-based Android study app. It helps you keep track of the applications you install/remove from your device.
        In addition, it captures the permission change you make. Joined users will form a community and users can see how other users are
        join the app. The data is stored safely and will not be used for any commercial purpose. Users are encouraged to answer the demographic
        questions to help us better understand how users use Android.
    </string>

    <string name="skip_tutorial">Skip</string>
    <string name="join_app">Start</string>
    <string name="set_up">Set up</string>
    <string name="ok">OK</string>
    <string name="done">Done</string>

    <string name="tutorial_how_title">How to use?</string>
    <string name="tutorial_how_description">
        App Install shows a list of apps that were installed after PrivaDroid was installed. Similarly,
        App Uninstall tab shows a list of apps that were uninstalled. Permission screen contains the grants/denys
        you gave to permission requests. Community shows an aggregated data from all users of this app. You can view your
        Advertisement ID and other information in the Profile tab.
    </string>

    <string name="tutorial_accessibility_service_title">Accessibility Service</string>
    <string name="tutorial_accessibility_service_description">
        Accessibility Service is required and used when the app needs to read the permission name and whether you grant/deny the
        permission request from an app. For example, Camera app requests Location access to you through a dialog and PrivaDroid will
        read the permission requested (Location) and whether you granted/denied it (Allow/Deny).
    </string>
    <string name="accessibility_rationale" description="Message shown to the user when toggling the accessibility permission for PrivaDroid">
        This permission is needed for PrivaDroid to be able to read permission name on the screen and detect click events when granting/denying permission requests.
    </string>

    <string name="tutorial_app_usage_title">App Usage Access</string>
    <string name="tutorial_app_usage_description">
        Usage access allows PrivaDroid to track what other apps you are using and how often, as well as your carrier, language settings,
        and other details.
    </string>

    <string name="community">Community</string>
    <string name="permission">Permission</string>
    <string name="app_uninstall">App Uninstall</string>
    <string name="app_install">App Install</string>
    <string name="profile">Profile</string>

    <string name="profile_screen_title">Profile</string>
    <string name="your_id">PrivaDroid ID</string>
    <string name="join_date">Join Date</string>

    <string name="empty" />
</resources>
